Guide to the Stanford University, Vice President for Business Affairs, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Civil Rights - Equal Employment Opportunity - Miscellaneous & General, 1967-1972 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Civil Rights - Equal Employment Opportunity - Stanford Correspondence & Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 94, Folder 24)
- Civil Rights, #1, 1957-1965 (Box 94, Folder 21)
- Civil Rights, #2, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 22)
- Civil Rights, #3, 1967-1968 (Box 94, Folder 23)
- Civil Rights, #4, 1969-1975 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Clark, Austin M., 1953-1962 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Clark, George A. & Helen V., 1938-1966 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Clark, Grace Birge, 1949-1960 (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Clinic Alterations - Legal Documents, 1963 (Box 103, Folder 6)
- Clinical Sciences - Legal Documents, 1961-1967 (Box 102, Folder 22)
- Clubhouse, The (formerly Women's Clubhouse), 1966-1971 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Cohn, Melvin, 1958-1962 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Coldwell, Banker & Co. - Survey, Lot 1, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Commercial Area - General, 1968-1973 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Commercial Area - South Palo Alto (C-3), 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Commercial Area - Storm Drain for Alson & Pickering - Hoffman, 1959-1960 (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Commercial Area - Storm Drainage, Page Mill Road, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Commercial Area - Underground Power & Telephone, 1959-1961 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Committee - Activities Center, 1955-1956 (Box 95, Folder 8)
- Committee - B & G - Authorizations #68-201 - 68-500, File 30, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- Committee - B & G - Authorizations #68-501 - 69-401, File 31, 1968-1969 (Box 95, Folder 10)
- Committee - B & G - Authorizations, #70-001 - 71-214, 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Committee - Buildings & Grounds - Board of Trustees, 1959-1961 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Committee - Buildings & Grounds - Board of Trustees, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Committee - Computer, 1963-1973 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Committee - Design, 1961-1966 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Committee - Facilities, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Committee - Faculty Housing Subcommittee, 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Committee - Food Service, Advisory Committee on, 1968-1970 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Committee - Governance of the Residential Area (Joint Subcommittee), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Committee - Guaranteed Stable Costs Plan, Ad Hoc - Adams, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Committee - Hospital (Stanford) - Architect, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Committee - Housing - Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Committee - Housing - Minutes, 1953-1957 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Committee - Housing (Joint), 1954 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Committee - Housing (Joint),1951 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Committee - Housing Advisory, Ad Hoc, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Committee - Interfraternity Board, 1963-1968 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Committee - Investments, Folder 2, 1951-1960 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Committee - Investments, Folder 3, 1959-1962 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Committee - Investments, Folder 4, 1961-1963 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Committee - Investments, Folder 5, 1963-1972 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Committee - Land and Building Development - Report of Master Plan for Campus Land Use, 1954-1956 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Committee - Land and Building Development, #1, 1950-1952 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Committee - Land and Building Development, #2, 1954-1956 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Committee - Land and Building Development, #3, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Committee - Land and Building Development, #4, 1957-1959 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Committee - Land and Building Development, #5, 1959-1964 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Committee - Land and Building Development, #6, 1964-1969 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Committee - Land and Building Development, #7, 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Committee - Land Development - Report to Board of Trustees, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Committee - Land Development (Board/Trustees), #1, 1952-1956 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Committee - Land Development (Board/Trustees), #2, 1956-1959 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Committee - Land Development (Board/Trustees), #3, 1959-1963 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Committee - Land Development (Board/Trustees), #4, 1963-1966 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Committee - Medical School Facilities - Purchasing & Stores, 1955-1957 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Committee - Medical School Facilities Planning - Minutes, 2, 1956-1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Committee - Medical School Facilities Planning, 1955-1957 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Committee - Medical School, Clinical, 1958-1960 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Committee - Non-Faculty Compensation (Presidential), 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Committee - Palo Alto - Stanford Hospital Steering Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Committee - Parking and Traffic (Presidential), 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Committee - Parking Problem (Presidential Committee) - D. B. Adams, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Committee - Patents, 1950-1961 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Committee - Petroleum Investments Fund, 1953-1966 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Committee - Planning Coordinating (formerly called "3 Vice Presidents Committe"), 1965-1968 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Committee - Plans Review - Completed Comments, 6, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Committee - Plans Review - Completed Comments, 7, 1961-1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Committee - Plans Review - Completed Comments, 8, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Committee - Plans Review - Comments (Completed), #3, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Committee - Plans Review - Comments (Completed), #4, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Committee - Plans Review - Miscellaneous comments, #9, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Committee - Plans Review Comments - Art Bldg., 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Committee - Plans Review Comments - Earth Sciences, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Committee - Plans Review Comments - Encina WW Remodeling, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Committee - Plans Review Comments - High Energy Physics Lab., 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Committee - Plans Review Comments - Jordan Hall Renovations, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Committee - Plans Review Comments (Completed), 5, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Committee - Plans Review Comments (Completed), 6, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Committee - Plans Review Comments (Completed), 7, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Committee - Plans Review Comments, 1 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Committee - Plans Review Comments, 2 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Committee - Public Excercises and Office of Public Events, 4, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Committee - Public Excercises and Office of Public Events, 5, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Committee - Public Exercises and Office of Public Events 2., 9/1/1965-12/31/1969 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Committee - Public Exercises and Office of Public Events 3., 1970-4/1/1991 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Committee - Public Health, 1959-1964 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Committee - Publications (Faculty), 1955 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Committee - Publications Board, 1966-1970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Committee - Publications Space Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Committee - Radiological Hazards Control, see: Safety Ins. & Health, 1963-1971 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Committee - Residence Operating - Dwight Adams and Joel Smith, 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Committee - Residence Program, 1962-1966 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Committee - Rush Policies (Ad Hoc), Student-Faculty Committee, 1962-1965 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Committee - Stanford Union, 1, 1959-1962 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Committee - Steering Committee - Study of Education at Stanford, Packer - Chairman, 1966-1969 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Committee - Student Faculty Employment, 1949-1970 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Committee - Student Publications, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Committee - Student Residences, 1960 Report on House Plan (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Committee - University Policy, 1959-1966 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Committee on Committees, 1959-1969 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Committee on Land and Buildings, March 14, 1978 (Binder) (Box 98)
- Committee on Land and Buildings, November 8, 1977 (Binder) (Box 98)
- Comparison of Costs (Peter Adamson), 1976 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Complaints, 1954-1972 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Compliments, 1945-1974 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Computation Center - Burroughs 5000, 1962-1968 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Computation Center - CDC v IBM - Yundt deposition materials, 1961-1970 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Computation Center - IBM Machines 7090-1401, 1961-1967 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Computation Center - IBM System 360/67, 1965-1968 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Computation Center Addition - Legal Documents, 408, 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 14)
- Computation Center, Folder 3, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Computation Center, Folder 4, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Computation Center, Folder 5, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Computation Center, Folder 6, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Computer Manuals (Box 86)
- Computer Time-Sharing Corporation - Exhibits (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Computers (Including Associate Provost for Computing), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Conley, Harry M. (Grazing Lease), #3, 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Conley, Harry M., #1, 1951-1960 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Conley, Harry M., #2, 1959-1969 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Conservation - Exhibits (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Construction - Engineers, 1957-1968 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Construction - New or Remodel - Procedures, Regulations, Permits, Ordinances, 1961-1969 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Construction and Remodeling - Procedures & Regulations - Academic Buildings and Actions of Board of Trustees, 1949-1961 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Construction Contracts - Stanford Forms, 1951-1971 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Construction Inspection - General, 1954-1963 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Construction Management Control System - Computerized System, 1973 (Binder) (Box 35)
- Construction Projects - Furnishings - Art Building, 1966-1968 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Construction Projects - Furnishings - Central Food Service, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Construction Projects - Furnishings - Encina West Wing (Food Res., Ec. Res, Contr.), 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Construction Projects - Furnishings - Escondido Village IV, 1962-1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Construction Projects - Furnishings - Fraternity Clusters, 1959-1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Construction Projects - Furnishings - General, 1966-1969 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Construction Projects - Furnishings - Jordan Hall Renovation - Psychology, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Construction Projects - Furnishings - Law School, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Construction Projects - Furnishings - President’s Office and Residence, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Construction Projects - Summary of Final Costs, Folder 1, 1947-1952 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Construction Projects - Summary of Final Costs, Folder 2, 1950-1969 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Consultant’s Services - McKee-Berger-Mansueto, Inc., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Contractors Construction - Land Development, 1950-1955 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Controller's Office - Administrative Data Processing - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Controller's Office - Administrative Data Processing - Exhibits (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Controller's Office - Research Administration, Folder 1, 1962-1966 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Controller's Office - Research Administration, Folder 2, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Controller's Office - Research Administration, Folder 3, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Controller's Office - Research Administration, Folder 4, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Controller's Office - Research Administration, Folder 5, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Controller's Office - Research Administration, Folder 6, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Controller's Office - Research Administration, Folder 7, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Controller's Office - Student Accounting - Delinquent Student Accounts #1, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Controller's Office - Student Accounts, #1, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Controller's Office, 1946-1960 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Controller's Office, #1, 1960-1966 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Controller's Office, #2, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Controller's Office, #3, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Controller's Office, #4, 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Cook's Oil Company, 1944-1956 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Cooper, K. J., 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Cooper, W. A. Estate, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Coover, Calvin, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Copyright - Ezra Pound - Rome Broadcasts, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Copyright - Publication Agreements with Others, 1971-1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Copyright - Strong Vocational Interest Blank (Press), #1, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Copyright Policy and Procedures, #1, 1955-1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Cost Accounting Standards Boards, 1972-1974 (Box 99, Folder 27)
- Cost Control Forms, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 42)
- Cost Estimating and Control, 1973 (Binder) (Box 35)
- Counseling and Testing, 1960-1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Cowell Student Health Center - Legal Documents, 1962-1967 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Coyote Hill Matters, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Craig, William G., 1956-1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Credit Card Agreements, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Credit Union, 1959-1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Cresap, McCormick & Paget - Management Consultants, 1963-1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Cressy, Andre - Estate of, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Crook, W. J., 1934-1946 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Cross, Helen Green, Mrs., 1936-1963 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Cross, Laura M. (Mrs. C. N.), 1935-1952 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- CS (City Services) Zoning, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Cubberley Royalties, 1947-1975 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Cushing, John E., 1954 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Cutler, Leland, 1936-1952 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Daniel, Ellis B., 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Davey, K. W., 1940-1963 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Davis, Stanley N., 1957-1967 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Dawson, Daryl Craig, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Dawson, Daryl Craig, - Personal, 1971-1975 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Dawson, Daryl Craig, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- Dawson, Daryl Craig, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 12)
- Dawson, Daryl Craig, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Dawson, Daryl Craig, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- Dean of Students, Folder 1, 1945-1964 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Dean of Students, Folder 2, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Dean of Students, Folder 3, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Dean of Students, Folder 4, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Dean of Students, Folder 5, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Dean, Everett S. & Lena, 1949-1955 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Dean's Office Expansion - Legal Documents, 1963 (Box 101, Folder 30)
- Delinquent Payments Reports, 1957-1968 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Delta Chi Bldg. Assn., 1934-1944 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Delta Chi Bldg. Assn., loan to, etc., 1922-1940 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Delta Chi Bldg. Assn., 1945-1955 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Delta Kappa Epsilon, Folder I, 1939-1954 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Delta Tau Delta (650 San Juan St.) - Rehabilitation, 754, 1972-1974 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Delta Upsilon, Folder I, 1939-1958 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Demolition - Cleveland Wrecking, 704, File V, 1967-1972 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Demolition & Canvass Costs, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Department - Aeronautics and Astronautics, 1958-1967 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Department - Aerospace Studies (formerly Dept. of Air Science), 1955-1971 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Department - Anatomy, 1935-1970 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Department - Applied Mechanics, 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Department - Art and Architecture - Pomodoro Bronzes, 1966-1972 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Department - Art and Architecture (Bavington Matter), 1928-1972 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Department - Art and Architecture, Art Gallery and Museum, #1, 1941-1961 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Department - Asian Language (& Center for Chinese & Japanese Studies), 1952-1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Department - Business, Graduate School of - ICAME Program, 1961-1964 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Department - Business, Graduate School of, 1, 1951-1960 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Department - Business, Graduate School of, 2, 1960-1966 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Department - Business, Graduate School of, 3, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Department - Business, Graduate School of, 4, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Department - Business, Graduate School of, 5, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Department - Chemical Engineering, 1962-1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Department - Chemistry, 1970-1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Department - Chemistry, 1, 1949-1959 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Department - Chemistry, 2, 1959-1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Department - Classics, 1941-1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Department - Communication (and the Institute for Communication Research), #1, 1961-1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Department - Computation Center ( Burroughs 220), 1958-1964 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Department - Corp. Yard Steam Plant, 1947-1960 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Department - Earth Sciences (formerly Mineral Science), 1950-1960 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Department - Earth Sciences, #1, 1960-1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Department - Economics, 1926-1970 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Department - Education - Stanford Center for Research & Development in Teaching ( SCRDT) #1, 1969-1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Department - Education, #1, 1957-1966 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Department - Education, #2, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Department - Education, School Planning Lab and S.C.S.D. - Exhibits (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Department - Education, School Planning Lab and S.C.S.D., 1970 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Department - Engineering - Radio Propagation, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Department - Engineering Security Move - AEL, 1954-1956 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Department - Engineering, School of, #1, 1941-1969 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Department - Food Research Institute, 1941-1972 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Department - French and Italian, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Department - Geography, 1950-1961 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Department - Hansen Laboratories - Biophysics, 1959-1966 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Department - Hansen Laboratories - High Energy #2, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Department - Hansen Laboratories - High Energy, #1, 1955-1969 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Department - Hansen Laboratories - Microwave #2, 1957-1971 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Department - Health Education (empty folder) (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Department - History, 1941-1963 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Department - Hopkins Marine Station - Acquisition of Additional Land, see: Outside Properties - Monterey Cty. Hovden (empty folder) (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Department - Hopkins Marine Station - University of California, 1947-1952 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Department - Hopkins Marine Station, #1, 1931-1957 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Department - Hopkins Marine Station, #2, 1957-1963 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Department - Hopkins Marine Station, #3, 1963-1965 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Department - Hopkins Marine Station, #4, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Department - Human Problems, Institute for the Study of, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Department - Humanities & Sciences, School of (and Humanitites - Special Programs), 1942-1969 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Department - Industrial Engineering, 1958-1970 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Department - Journalism Division - Communications & Journalism, 1941-1958 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Department - Latin American Studies, 1961-1974 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Department - Law, #1, 1958-1972 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Department - Libraries - Lighting Plan, 1941-1956 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Department - Mathematical Studies in the Social Sciences, Institute, 1964-1972 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Department - Mathematics; Statistics, 1942-1974 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Department - Mechanical Engineering - Ryan Lab - #2, 1964-1971 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Department - Mechanical Engineering - Ryan Lab - Nuclear Reactor Correspondence, 1959-1967 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Department - Mechanical Engineering - Ryan Lab - Nuclear Reactor Prelim. Contract Drafts, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Department - Mechanical Engineering - Ryan Lab - Purchase of Nuclear Reactor from GE, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Department - Medical School - Letters from Dr. Cutting, 1953-1956 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Department - Medicine, School of - Affiliation Agreements, 1955-1966 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Department - Medicine, School of - Affiliation Agreements, 1967-1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Department - Medicine, School of - Construction, A to M, 1965-1971 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Department - Medicine, School of - Construction, N to Z, 1965-1971 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Department - Medicine, School of - NASA Contracts, 1966-1973 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Department - Medicine, School of, #1, 1950-1962 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Department - Medicine, School of, #3, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Department - Medicine, School of, #4, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Department - Medicine, School of, #5, 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Department - Medicine, School of, #6, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Department - Medicine, School of, G to H, 1962-1970 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Department - Military - ROTC, NROTC, 1953-1959 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Department - Military Science, 1960-1966 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Department - Military/Property Custodian - Air Force ROTC, 1958-1971 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Department - Military/Property Custodian - Army ROTC, 1966-1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Department - Modern European Languages, see: Department - German, Slavic or Spanish, 1941-1968 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Department - Music, #1, 1958-1966 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Department - Music, #2, 1967-1972 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Department - Naval Science, 1960-1971 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Department - Nursing, School of - Affiliation Agreements, 1955-1973 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Department - P.E. & Athletics - Men - US-USSR Track Meet, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Department - Philosophy, 1950-1967 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Department - Physical Education & Athletics - Men, #6, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Department - Physical Education & Athletics - Men, Folder 1, 1951-1962 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Department - Physical Education & Athletics - Men, Folder 2, 1962-1964 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Department - Physical Education & Athletics - Men, Folder 5, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Department - Physical Education & Athletics - Women, #2, 1958-1974 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Department - Physical Education & Athletics - Women, 1950-1957 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Department - Physical Therapy, 1942-1948 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Department - Physics - Van de Graaf Machine Installation - Exhibits (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Department - Physics, 1951-1962 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Department - Physiology, 1941-1964 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Department - Political Science, 1942-1974 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Department - Purchasing, 1, 1950-1959 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Department - School Mathematics Study Group, #1, 1962-1969 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Department - Speech & Drama - Shakespearean Festival, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Department - Speech & Drama - Stanford Repertory Theater, #1, 1965-1967 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Department - Speech & Drama - Stanford Repertory Theater, File #2, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Department - Speech & Drama - Summer Festival, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Department - Speech & Drama - Summer Festival, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Department - Speech & Drama - Summer Festival, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Department - Speech & Drama - Summer Festival, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Department - Speech & Drama - Summer Festival, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Department - Stanford Electronics Laboratories, 1, 1954-1961 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Department - Stanford Electronics Laboratories, 2, 1962-1965 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Department - Systematic Biology - Vanderbilt Foundation, 1961-1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Department - Systematic Biology - Vanderbilt Foundation, 1964-1970 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Department - Systematic Biology, 1941-1967 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Department - Systematic Biology, see also: Pioneer Yacht, 1954-1961 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Department -Sociology, 1959-1975 (Box 14, Folder 18)